Guide to the Student Christian Movement in New England Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- College Files, 1929-1969; Series II
  - Yale University Reports, 1940-1963 (Box 18, Folder 248)
  - Yale University Program materials (Box 18, Folder 249)
  - Yale University Program materials (Box 18, Folder 250)
  - Yale University, Episcopal Church at, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - Yale University, United Student Fellowship (UCC ), 1950-1964 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - Yale University, Wesley Foundation; Westminster Foundation, 1958-1964 (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Miscellaneous church groups participating in SCM in NE, 1952-1967 (Box 18, Folder 254)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence with local group representatives (Box 18, Folder 255)
  - Miscellaneous local group reports to YMCA, 1941-1942 (Box 18, Folder 256)
  - Miscellaneous local group reports to YMCA, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 257)
  - Miscellaneous local group reports to YMCA, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 258)
  - Miscellaneous local group reports to YMCA, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 259)
- Conferences, 1926-1977; Series III
  The conference records are arranged alphabetically by the name of the conference and on a yearly basis if the conference was recurring.
  - Annual Representative Assembly (For Assembly Reports see: Series VI, Publications), 1955-1959 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - Annual Representative Assembly, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 261)
  - Annual Representative Assembly, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - Annual Representative Assembly, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Annual Representative Assembly, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - Annual Representative Assembly, 1967,n.d. (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - Becket, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 266)
  - Bible Study Retreats, 1950,1951 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Boston Area Fall Conferences, 1944-1950 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Boston Area Fall Conferences, 1952-1955 (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Camp Hazen Seminar, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Christian Vocation and the Legal Profession Conference, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 271)
  - Churchmanship Conference, 1941,1948 (Box 19, Folder 272)
  - Commission Conference, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 273)
  - Commission Leaders Conferences, 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 274)
  - Conference on Education for Marriage, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 275)
  - Conference on Effective Christian Citizenship, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 276)
  - Conference on Worship, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 277)
  - Connecticut Valley Conference on the Christian Way of Life, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Connecticut Valley Conferences (Northfield), 1935-1941 (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Connecticut Valley Conferences (Northfield), 1942-1943 (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Connecticut Valley Conferences (including Northfield), 1944-1946 (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Connecticut Valley Conferences (including Northfield), 1947-1953 (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Connecticut Valley Conferences (including Northfield), 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - Connecticut Valley Conferences (including Northfield), 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - Consultation on Higher Education and World Change, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 285)
  - Eastern New England Conferences, 1950-1955 (Box 20, Folder 286)
  - Eastern New England Conferences, 1956-1961 (Box 20, Folder 287)
  - Ecumenical Conference, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 288)
  - Episcopal Church Vocational Conference for College Women, 1945-1948 (Box 21, Folder 289)
  - European Seminar, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 290)
  - Faculty-Student Conferences, 1929-1931 (Box 21, Folder 291)
  - Fall Conferences, 1962-1968 (Box 21, Folder 292)
  - Four College Conferences, 1947,1948 (Box 21, Folder 293)
  - Full Employment Conference, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 294)
  - Groton Conference, 1942-1950 (Box 21, Folder 295)
  - Housing Conference, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 296)
  - Labor, Rural Problems Conferences, 1941,1942,n.d. (Box 21, Folder 297)
  - Leadership Conferences, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 298)
  - Leadership Conferences, 1940-1945 (Box 21, Folder 299)
  - Leadership Conferences, 1946-1953 (Box 21, Folder 300)
  - Leadership Conferences, 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 301)
  - Legislative Assembly (For Assembly Reports see: Series VI, Publications), 1934-1946 (Box 21, Folder 302)
  - Legislative Assembly, 1947-1949 (Box 21, Folder 303)
  - Legislative Assembly, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 304)
  - Legislative Assembly, 1951-1954 (Box 21, Folder 305)
  - Life and Mission of the Church Conference, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 306)
  - Life of the Church Conference, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 307)
  - Life of the Church Conference, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 308)
  - Life of the Church Conference, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 309)
  - Life of the Church Conference, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - Life of the Church Conference, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Life of the Church Conference, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 312)
  - Maine Area Conference, 1939-1949 (Box 22, Folder 313)
  - Maine Area Conference, 1950-1958 (Box 22, Folder 314)
  - Maritime-New England Conference, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 315)
  - Midwinter Conference, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 316)
  - Midwinter Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 317)
  - Midwinter Conference, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 318)
  - Miscellaneous conferences, 1936-1967,n.d. (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - National Student Assembly, 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 320)
  - National Student Assembly, 1950-1967,n.d. (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - National Student Christian Consultation and follow-up, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - New England Student Intergroup Conference, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - North American Student Conference on Christian Frontiers (Froncon), 1947 (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - Northfield Conference for College Women, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Northfield Summer Conference, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 326)
  - Northfield Summer Conference at Camp Becket, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 327)
  - O-AT-KA, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 328)
  - O-AT-KA, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 329)
  - O-AT-KA, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 330)
  - O-AT-KA, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 331)
  - O-AT-KA, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 332)
  - O-AT-KA, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 333)
  - O-AT-KA, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - O-AT-KA, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 335)
  - O-AT-KA, addendum, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - O-AT-KA, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 336)
  - O-AT-KA, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - O-AT-KA, addendum, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - O-AT-KA, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 338)
  - O-AT-KA, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 339)
  - O-AT-KA, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 340)
  - O-AT-KA, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 341)
  - O-AT-KA, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 342)
  - O-AT-KA, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 343)
  - O-AT-KA, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 344)
  - O-AT-KA, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 345)
  - O-AT-KA, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - O-AT-KA, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - O-AT-KA, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - O-AT-KA, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - O-AT-KA, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 350)
  - O-AT-KA, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - O-AT-KA, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - O-AT-KA, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - O-AT-KA, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - O-AT-KA, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - O-AT-KA, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 356)
  - O-AT-KA, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 357)
  - O-AT-KA, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 358)
  - O-AT-KA, 1967,n.d. (Box 26, Folder 359)
  - Opocensky Conference, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 360)
  - Presidents' Conference, 1934-1939 (Box 26, Folder 361)
  - Seminar on Anti-Semitism, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 362)
  - Seminars for Workers with Students, 1941-1947 (Box 26, Folder 363)
  - Spring Forum, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 364)
  - Staff-Clergy-Faculty Conferences, 1933-1940 (Box 26, Folder 365)
  - Staff-Clergy-Faculty Conferences, 1941-1944 (Box 26, Folder 366)
  - Staff-Clergy-Faculty Conferences, 1945-1950 (Box 26, Folder 367)
  - Staff-Clergy-Faculty Conferences, 1951-1959 (Box 26, Folder 368)
  - Staff-Clergy-Faculty Conferences, 1961-1967 (Box 26, Folder 369)
  - State College Consultations, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 370)
  - State Teachers College Conferences, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 371)
  - State Teachers College Conferences, 1951-1952 (Box 27, Folder 372)
  - State Teachers College Conferences, 1954-1956 (Box 27, Folder 373)
  - Student Volunteer Conference on Christian Service overseas, Northfield, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Summer Study Retreat, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 375)
  - Symposium on the City, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 376)
  - United Student Christian Council Conferences, 1956,1957 (Box 27, Folder 377)
  - Vocational Conferences, 1944-1954 (Box 27, Folder 378)
  - Weekend Conversation on Missions, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 379)
  - Wooster Planning Conference on the World Mission of the Church, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 380)
  - World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 381)
  - World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - World Conference on Church, Community and State, Oxford, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 383)
  - World Mission of the Christian Church/ Mission of the World Church Conferences, 1942-1954 (Box 27, Folder 384)
- Program Materials, 1938-1966, n.d.; Series IV
  This series is divided into four sections:
  A. Main office program notebook. From 1938 through 1942 the S.C.M. main office maintained a notebook containing copies of all communiques, announcements and printed material related to its ongoingprogram.
  B. Projects, programs. Summer and other special projects of the S.C.M. are documented, the material arranged alphabetically by the name of the project.
  C. Topical source material. Miscellaneous material arranged alphabetically by topic.
  D. Audiovisual material. Tapes and films used in or recording S.C.M. programs.
  - Main office program notebook, 1938 Feb-1938 Sep (Box 28, Folder 385)
  - Main office program notebook, 1938 Oct-1938 Dec (Box 28, Folder 386)
  - Main office program notebook, 1939 Jan-1939 Feb (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Main office program notebook, 1939 Apr-1939 Jun (Box 28, Folder 388)
  - Main office program notebook, 1939 Jul-1939 Oct (Box 28, Folder 389)
  - Main office program notebook, 1939 Nov-1940 Jan (Box 28, Folder 390)
  - Main office program notebook, 1940 Feb-1940 Apr (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - Main office program notebook, 1940 May-1940 Aug (Box 29, Folder 392)
  - Main office program notebook, 1940 Sep-1940 Nov (Box 29, Folder 393)
  - Main office program notebook, 1940 Dec-1941 Feb (Box 29, Folder 394)
  - Main office program notebook, 1941 Mar (Box 29, Folder 395)
  - Main office program notebook, 1941 Apr-1941 Jul (Box 29, Folder 396)
  - Main office program notebook, 1941 Dec-1942 Dec (Box 29, Folder 397)
  - Projects: Adelaide T. Case Memorial Fund (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - Projects: Africa Project - W.S.C.F., 1958 (Box 30, Folder 399)
  - Projects: Bill Ellis Fund, 1947-1948 (Box 30, Folder 400)
  - Projects: Bruce Jones Fund (Box 30, Folder 401)
  - Projects: College Embassies, 1938-1944 (Box 30, Folder 402)
  - Projects: Core Group Program, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 403)
  - Projects: Core Group Program (Box 30, Folder 404)
  - Projects: Food for Europe, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 405)
  - Projects: Jim Robinson Fund, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 406)
  - Projects: Koinonia Farm Project, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 407)
  - Projects: Koinonia Farm Project (Box 30, Folder 408)
  - Projects: Koinonia Farm Project (Box 30, Folder 409)
  - Projects: Koinonia Farm Project (Box 30, Folder 410)
  - Projects: Margaret Richards Memorial, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 411)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Training Seminar, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Project: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Training Seminar, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Seminar, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Training Seminar, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Seminar, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Seminar, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Seminar, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 418)
  - Projects: Martha's Vineyard Leadership Seminar, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 419)
  - Projects: Miscellaneous Summer Programs (Box 31, Folder 420)
  - Projects: New England Students in Agriculture, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 421)
  - Projects: Northern Student Movement Coordinating Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 422)
  - Projects: Northern Student Movement Coordinating Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 423)
  - Projects: Presidents' Summer School (Box 31, Folder 424)
  - Projects: Roxbury Summer Service Project, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 425)
  - Projects: Roxbury Summer Service Project, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 426)
  - Projects: SCM-Summer College Educational Project, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 427)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 428)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 429)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 430)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 431)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 432)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 433)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 434)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 435)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 436)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, Hartford, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 437)
  - Projects: Students in Industry Project, New Haven, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 438)
  - Projects: USA-USSR Student Exchange, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 439)
  - Topical: Alcohol (Box 33, Folder 440)
  - Bible Study (Box 33, Folder 441)
  - Bibliographies (Box 33, Folder 442)
  - Brazil, 1963-1965 (Box 33, Folder 443)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 33, Folder 444)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 33, Folder 445)
  - Civil Rights - Southern Courier (Box 33, Folder 446)
  - Civil Rights - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Civilian Defense (Box 33, Folder 448)
  - Coffee houses (Box 33, Folder 449)
  - Communism, USSR (Box 33, Folder 450)
  - Conservation (Box 33, Folder 451)
  - Disarmament (Box 33, Folder 452)
  - Ethnic Minorities (Box 33, Folder 453)
  - Fraternities, sororities (Box 33, Folder 454)
  - Freshman orientation (Box 33, Folder 455)
  - Foreign students (Box 33, Folder 456)
  - Housing (Box 33, Folder 457)
  - Intercollegian Magazine (Box 33, Folder 458)
  - Judaism (Box 33, Folder 459)
  - Peace (Box 34, Folder 460)
  - Peace (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Peace (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - Peace (Box 34, Folder 463)
  - Program techniques (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Public Affairs (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - Race relations (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - Race relations (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Race relations (Box 35, Folder 468)
  - Race relations (Box 35, Folder 469)
  - Race relations (Box 35, Folder 470)
  - Race relations (Box 35, Folder 471)
  - Race relations (Box 35, Folder 472)
  - Radical Education (Box 35, Folder 473)
  - Status of Women (Box 35, Folder 474)
  - Student movements (Box 35, Folder 475)
  - United Nations (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Universal Military Training (Box 35, Folder 477)
  - Vietnam War (Box 35, Folder 478)
  - Wartime issues (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - Worship (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Worship (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Worship (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 36, Folder 483)
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 37, Folder 484)
  - Audiovisual materials Audiovisual materials (see: Oversize materials) (Box 38, Folder 485)
- Historical Records and Reports, 1934-1968; Series V
  A variety of material is included in this series including the S.C.M. in New England constitution and by-laws, legal agreements, alumni information, lists of affiliated groups and a collection of miscellaneous documents which seem to have been gathered together during the evaluation process of 1966 in order to trace the history of the Movement.
  - Alumni information: Names and addresses, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 486)
  - Alumni information: Names and addresses, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 487)
  - Alumni information: Names and addresses, 1965,1967 (Box 39, Folder 488)
  - Alumni information: Newsletters (Box 39, Folder 489)
  - Constitutions and by-laws (Box 39, Folder 490)
  - Documents tracing history of SCM, 1934-1935 (Box 39, Folder 491)
  - Documents tracing history of SCM, 1938-1947 (Box 39, Folder 492)
  - Documents tracing history of SCM, 1948-1959 (Box 39, Folder 493)
  - Documents tracing history of SCM, 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 494)
  - Documents tracing history of SCM, 1967-1968 (Box 39, Folder 495)
  - Documents tracing history of SCM, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 496)
  - Legal agreements, 1938-1967 (Box 40, Folder 497)
  - Lists - Affiliated groups, 1937-1949 (Box 40, Folder 498)
  - Lists - Affiliated groups, 1950-1963,n,d. (Box 40, Folder 499)
  - Lists - Committee membership, 1938-1957,n.d. (Box 40, Folder 500)
  - SCM during World War II, 1941-1942 (Box 40, Folder 501)
  - Tenth Anniversary Dinner, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 502)
- Publications, 1934-1967; Series VI
  The official publications of the S.C.M. in New England are grouped together by title.
  - Assembly reports, 1934-1936 (Box 41, Folder 503)
  - Assembly reports, 1938-1942 (Box 41, Folder 504)
  - Assembly reports, 1943-1949 (Box 41, Folder 505)
  - Assembly reports, 1950-1954 (Box 41, Folder 506)
  - Assembly reports, 1955-1957 (Box 41, Folder 507)
  - Assembly reports, 1958-1961 (Box 41, Folder 508)
  - Assembly reports, 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 509)
  - Assembly reports, 1964-1967 (Box 42, Folder 510)
  - ''Bulletins", 1935 (Box 42, Folder 511)
  - Brochures, miscellany, 1937, 1962, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 512)
  - Directories of the SCM-NE (Box 42, Folder 513)
  - Ecumenical Newsletter, 1964-1966 (Box 42, Folder 514)
  - Expression, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 515)
  - Interpreting the N.E.S.C.M., 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 516)
  - The New Englander, 1947-1957 (Box 42, Folder 517)
  - "Newsletters", 1935-1951 (Box 42, Folder 518)
  - Telstar, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 519)
  - Yankee Student, 1960-1967 (Box 42, Folder 520)
  - Yankee Student Opinion, 1963-1965 (Box 42, Folder 521)
- Related Groups, 1930-1974; Series VII
  The material in this series is organized alphabetical y by the name of the related organization or denomination.
  - General policy - Consultations of Sponsoring and Participating Agencies, 1955-1966 (Box 43, Folder 522)
  - General Policy - Miscellaneous, 1953-1964 (Box 43, Folder 523)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1949-1965 (Box 43, Folder 524)
  - Baptist Student Foundation, 1951-1967 (Box 43, Folder 525)
  - Christian Churches (Disciples of Christ), 1962 (Box 43, Folder 526)
  - Christian Fellowship Foundation/ Packard Manse, 1951-1966 (Box 43, Folder 527)
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 528)
  - Congregational Christian Churches Boston Student Workers r Council, 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 529)
  - Congregational Christian Churches Correspondence of Wm. Wimer, 1946-1948 (Box 43, Folder 530)
  - Congregational Christian Churches Miscellaneous, 1940-1962 (Box 43, Folder 531)
  - Congregational Christian Churches "Student Life Notes", 1945-1947 (Box 43, Folder 532)
  - Council for Religion in Independent Schools, Inc., 1960-1965 (Box 43, Folder 533)
  - Evangelical and Reformed Church, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 534)
  - International Student Service, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 535)
  - Interseminary Movement, 1930-1944 (Box 43, Folder 536)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1955-1959 (Box 43, Folder 537)
  - Laymen's Academy for Oecumenical Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 538)
  - Leyden International Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 43, Folder 539)
  - The Liste Fellowship, Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 43, Folder 540)
  - Lutheran groups, 1959-1965 (Box 44, Folder 541)
  - Massachusetts Council for Constitutional Rights, 1953-1955 (Box 44, Folder 542)
  - Massachusetts Council of Churches, 1952-1957 (Box 44, Folder 543)
  - Methodist Groups, 1947-1959 (Box 44, Folder 544)
  - Methodist groups, 1960-1967 (Box 44, Folder 545)
  - National Council of Churches, 1948-1963 (Box 44, Folder 546)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council, 1939,1950 (Box 44, Folder 547)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1954-1963 (Box 44, Folder 548)
  - National Student Christian Federation, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 549)
  - New England Commission for United Ministries In Higher Education (see also: RG 54), 1965-1968 (Box 44, Folder 550)
  - New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education, 1969-1974 (Box 44, Folder 551)
  - Newman Apostolate - Boston, 1965-1967 (Box 45, Folder 552)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1948-1958 (Box 45, Folder 553)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1959-1964,n.d. (Box 45, Folder 554)
  - Puerto Rican Student Christian Movement, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 555)
  - Student Christian Movement of Greater Boston, 1930-1940 (Box 45, Folder 556)
  - Student Christian Movement of Greater Boston, 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 557)
  - Student Christian Movement of New York State, 1951-1966 (Box 45, Folder 558)
  - Student Christian Movement in New York, 1927-1955 (Box 51, Folder 3-5)
    Includes filmstrip and script "Christian Student Life in America"
  - Student Worker's Council of Greater Boston, 1935-1952 (Box 45, Folder 559)
  - Student Volunteer Movement, 1943-1961 (Box 45, Folder 560)
  - Unitarian groups, 1948-1956 (Box 45, Folder 561)
  - United Campus Christian Fellowship, 1961-1967 (Box 46, Folder 562)
  - United Church of Christ, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 563)
  - United Service Organizations, Inc., 1944-1946 (Box 46, Folder 564)
  - United Student Fellowship, 1956-1960 (Box 46, Folder 565)
  - University Christian Mission, 1953,n.d. (Box 46, Folder 566)
  - University Christian Movement, Cleveland week, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 567)
  - University Christian Movement Look UP and Live TV Series, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 568)
  - University Christian Movement Miscellaneous program material, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 569)
  - University Christian Movement Organization, 1966-1969 (Box 46, Folder 570)
  - University Christian Movement Publications, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 571)
  - Westminster Foundation in New England, 1959-1964,n.d. (Box 46, Folder 572)
  - World Council of Churches, 1957,1959,n.d. (Box 46, Folder 573)
  - World Fellowship, Inc., 1954 (Box 46, Folder 574)
  - World Student Service Fund, 1939-1948,n.d. (Box 47, Folder 575)
  - World University Service, 1946-1966,n.d. (Box 47, Folder 576)
  - World's Student Christian Federation, 1934-1957 (Box 47, Folder 577)
  - World's Student Christian Federation, 1958-1968 (Box 47, Folder 578)
  - Y.M.C.A. / National Council of Student Associations, 1925-1928 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Y.M.C.A. (see also: Record Group 58), 1934,1957-1965 (Box 47, Folder 579)
  - Y.M.C.A. (see also: RG 58), 1940,1956-1966 (Box 47, Folder 580)
  - Y.W.C.A., 1932-1966 (Box 47, Folder 581)
  - Y.W.C.A. Monthly Reports, Sep 1938-Jun 1940 (Box 47, Folder 582)
- Financial Material, 1929-1969; Series VIII
  Included in this series are:
  A. Account records (1939-1943) (1953-1954)
  B. Budgets and statements
  C. Correspondence with individuals and organizations
  D. Minutes and reports of the Finance Committee
  - Account Book, 1953-1954 (Box 48, Folder 583)
  - Miscellaneous account records, 1939-1943 (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Budgets, statements, 1931-1937 (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Budgets, statements, 1938-1955 (Box 48, Folder 586)
  - Budgets, statements, 1956-1964 (Box 48, Folder 587)
  - Budgets, statements, 1965-1969 (Box 48, Folder 588)
  - Contribution records, 1932-1934 (Box 49, Folder 589)
  - Contribution records, 1935-1956 (Box 49, Folder 590)
  - Contribution records, 1957-1966 (Box 49, Folder 591)
  - Correspondence - Finance Committee, 1935-1967 (Box 49, Folder 592)
  - Correspondence - Form letter appeals, 1932-1968 (Box 49, Folder 593)
  - Correspondence with foundations: Hazen Foundation, 1932-1952 (Box 49, Folder 594)